Finding Aid for the Edwin Sheffield Gleaves Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- LS 307/LIS 3070, LITERARY RESEARCH AND BIBLIOGRAPHY LIS 3710, LATIN AMERICAN SEMINAR LS 320/3200, MICROGRAPHICS LS/ED 260A, INTRODUCTION TO MEDIA STUDIES
  - LS 320 -- Gleaves, E. S. “A Microforms program for the Duckworth Libraries. ..” (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - LS 320 -- Formats and Standards (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - LS 320 -- “Microforms: A History of Benign Neglect (JAL) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - LS 320 -- Micrographics: An eventful Forty Years -- What Next? (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - LS 320 -- JUL (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - LS 320 -- Microform Readers. Sourcebook of Library Technology (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Xerox University Microfilms (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eastman Kodak Company (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - LIS 3200 -- Surging Serial Costs: the Microfiche solution (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - LIS 3200 -- National Micrographics Association (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - LIS 3200 -- “Micrographics Yesterday” (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - LIS 3200 -- “MicroVAX 800” (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - LIS 3200 -- “The Reader’s Road Atlas” (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - LIS 3200 -- “This Is Microprint” (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - LIS 3200 -- Resources for the Study of Microforms (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ERIC Information -- Clearinghouse on Information Resources (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Library Technology Reports (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Microformatos -- Calulos Para el Costo... “ (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Microform Review -- Annual Library Microform Conference (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - LS 320 -- Schedule of 5th Annual Library Microform Conference (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - LS 320 -- How to Use ERIC (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 3-M Company Advertisement... COM, etc. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - LS 320 -- “Microforms: What They Are and how They Are Used” (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - LS 320 -- Why Microforms? (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - LS 320 -- The New Contemporary Kitchen Library (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - LS 320 -- Monarch Notes on Microfiche (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - LIS 3200 -- ERIC Printouts (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - LS 320 -- Ring King Visible (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - LS 320 -- Reprint of ED 046-403 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - “Literary and Library Prizes” (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - LS/English 307 -- A Bibliographical Guide to the Study of Contemporary American Writers (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - LS/English 307 -- Book Reviewing: “The Fine Art of Literary Mayham” (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Requiem for a Reviewer (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - LS 307 -- Assignment -- “Some Books Every Student of Literature Should Read” (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Breaking the Language Barrier (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - LS/English 307 -- (Peabody) Surveys and Histories (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - LS/English 307 -- Tanselle Article (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- “Looking Backward” (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Bibliographical Verification (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- The Oxford Companion to Critics: Study in Biography (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - LS/English 307 -- Exams -- Bibliographical Form (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Poetry -- “Time and Death,” “Death Be Not Proud” (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- The Comparative Review: Political Satire (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Survey of the Literature (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Gleaves, E. S. The Textual Revolution (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - LS 307 -- Tanselle, “The Periodical Literature of English and American Bibliography” (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - LS 307 -- “The Periodical Literature of English and American Bibliography” (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - “Literary Manslaughter” (ESG) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - LS 307 -- “Hemingway and Baroja: Studies in Spiritual Anarchism” (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - LS 307 -- Altick, “The Unsung Scholar,” The Scholar Adventurers (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - LS/ED 260A -- Outline of Topics (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - LS/ED 260A -- Objectives of the Course, etc. (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - ED 260 -- Educational media (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - ED//LS 260 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - LS 3710 -- Latin American Seminar (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Grants for Libraries: A Highly Selective Bibliography (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Librarianship 442 (Washington) -- Syllabus, Reading Lists, Exams (Box 8, Folder 59)
- LS221/LIS 2210, SELECTION/COLLECTION DEVELOPMENT
  - LS 221 -- The Best-Seller Program (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - LIS 2210/3070 -- Prices of Reference Book (Transparencies) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - LS 221 -- Best Sellers (TR) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - LS 221 -- (Peabody) Articles (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - LS 221 -- The Best-Seller Program (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - LS 221 -- The Best-Seller Program (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - LS 221 -- Reading Lists (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Designed for College” (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - LS 221 -- Bookselling in the Sunbelt PW-11/15/76 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - LS 221 -- Varieties of Readers and Reading in, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - LIS 2210 -- Gleaves “Literary Manslaughter” (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - LS 327 -- Assignments “Classics and Best Sellers” (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - LIS 2210 -- 1983 Consumer Research Study on Reading (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - LIS 2210 -- Budgets (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- TV (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - LIS 2210 -- Censorship -- Textbooks (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - “What to Do Before the Censor Comes and After” (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - LIS 2210 -- Tampa Public Library (Censorship Case) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - LS 210 -- Publishing Trade (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Reading in America, 1928-1946 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - LIS 2210 -- Reading in America, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Reading Lists -- ALA (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Reading Lists -- Keys to Good Reading (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - LIS 2210 -- “General Principles of Selection” (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - LS 221 -- “Overlooked Books” (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Basic Publications for the Publisher and the Book Trade (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Book Clubs (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - LS 2210 -- (ALA) Development of a Materials Selection Program; Katz Collection Development Policy (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - LS 221 -- “Policies and Procedures for Selection of Instructional Material” (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - LS 221 -- (Peabody) Book Selection Tools (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - LIS 2210 -- Materials Selection Tools, (Spring 1983) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - IS/English 307 -- Book Reviewing (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Acquisition Policies and Procedures (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - LIS 2210 -- Book Selection Media: Types and Examples (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - LS 221 -- Materials Selection Policy (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Translation -- Articles, etc. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - LS 221 -- Editions, Series, Translations (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - LS 221 -- Editions and Series (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - LIS 2210 -- Book in Other Languages, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - LIS 2210 -- WPLN Program Guide: Understanding Music Code (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - LS 221 -- Selection Aids: Non-Book Materials (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - LIS 2210 -- Microcomputer Software (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - LS 221 -- Un Programa de Adquisicion Cooperativa de publiciones Periodcas (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - LS 221 -- Academic Libraries (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - LIS 2210 -- Methods of Evaluation Methods and Examples (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - LS 221 -- Coutts Library Services and JUL (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - LIS 2210 -- Evaluation of Collections (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - LIS 2210 -- Selection Policies -- Public Libraries (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Asheim -- Who Selects for Whom (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - LIS 2210 -- A Droll Role Play; Creationism vs. Evolution (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - LIS 2210 -- Creationism vs. Evolution (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- “Readings on intellectual Freedom” (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- Articles (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- Are You Running With Me Jesus (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - LS 221 -- (Peabody) Examinations (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - LIS 2210 -- Study Guide for Final Examination (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - LIS 2210 -- Final Examination, Fall, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - LIS 2210 -- Final Examination, Spring, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - LIS 2210 -- Final Examination, Spring, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - LIS 2210 -- Final Examination, Summer, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- LS 307/LIS 3070, LITERARY RESEARCH AND BIBLIOGRAPHY
  - LS/English 307 -- Bibliography and Literature Research, Bibliography (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - LS/English 307 -- Bibliography and Literature Research, Assignments (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - LS/English 307 -- Bibliography and Literature Research (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Bibliographical Essay (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - LIS 3070 -- Review for ARBA (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - LS/English 307 -- Bibliographies and Study Guides (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - LIS 3070 -- Flannery O’Connor, Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - LS 307 -- Originals (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - LS 307 -- Pathfinders and Other Library Research Guides (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - LS 307 -- Proposal for Books (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - LS 307 -- Descriptive Bibliography: To Be or Not To Be (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - LS/English 307 -- Washington Irving (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Problems in Bibliography (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - LIS 3070 -- Characteristics of Written Scholarship in American Literature: A Citation Study” (Budd) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - LS 307 -- Journals and Reviews (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - LS 307 -- William Pell, “Facts of Scholarly Publishing,” PMCA 88, Spring, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - LS 307 -- Journals and Literary Reviews (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - LIS 3070 -- Patterson’s Literary Research Guide; Some Reference Questions (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - LIS 3070 -- “The Literary Elite” (ESG) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - LS 307 -- The Basic Core (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - LIS 3070 -- Dictionaries (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - LS 307 -- Textual Study -- Emily Dickinson (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - LS 307 -- “Bibliography” (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - LS/English 307 -- Bibliography and Literature Research: Course of Study (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- What Is In A Name? (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Poetry -- Six Poems (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - LS/English 307 -- Quiz Riverside Editions (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Literary Scholarship (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Detection of Error (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Detection of Error (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - LS/English 307 -- Glossolalia Literaria (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - LIS 3070 -- Computers and Literature (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - LS 307 -- Clossolalia and Literaria (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Poetry -- “Binsley Poplars” and “Commuions” (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - LS/English 307 -- Cartoon of David Levine (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - LS/English 307 -- H128a or Emily Unedited (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - LIS 3070 -- Washington Irving, The Sketch Book (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - LS 307 -- “Some Scholarly Occupations” (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Literature in Translation” (ESG) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - LS 331 -- Letters to Literary Tabby (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - LS 307 -- The Spirit of Scholarship (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - LS 307 -- Johnson, Thomas H., ed. The Poems of Emily Dickinson (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - LS/English 307 -- Examinations (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - LS 307 -- Eaters of the Dead: Stranger Than Fiction (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- A Recherché du Livres Perdus (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - LS/English 307 -- Quiz Saturday Review (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - LS/English 307 -- Supplementary Materials (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - LS/English 307 -- Review of Reviews (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - LS/English 307 -- Quiz -- “The Common Reader and the Uncommon Critic” (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - LS/English 307 -- Reference Bibliography: A Tentative Taxonomy (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - LS/English 307 -- The Bibliographical Bard: Some Reference Questions (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - LS/English 307 -- William Pell, “Facts of Scholarly Publishing,” PMCA 88, Spring, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - LS/English 307 -- Assignments -- Quotations in Context: The Whole Truth (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Poetry -- “To His Toy Mistress” (Marvell and Meinke) (Box 10, Folder 54)
- LS 327, READING INTERESTS LS 385, EDUCATION FOR LIBRARIANSHIP
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Reviews of Reviews (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Articles (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - LS 327 -- Services to the Blind and Physically handicapped (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Sights and Sounds Showcase (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Profile of the Changing Library (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - LS 327 -- English Journalism (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Course of Study (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Notable Books Assignment (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Bibliographies (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Examinations (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Assignments (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Assignments on Best Sellers (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - LS 327 -- Assignments -- “Oral Reports” (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - LS 327 -- Assignments on American Issues Forum (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - LS 327 -- Bibliographies (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - LS 327 -- Assignments -- Reading Profile and Reading Plan (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - LS 327 -- Parallel Reading Lists (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Parallel Readings (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Assignment: Magazine Biographies (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Assignments (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - LS 327 -- Reading Interests -- Reserve Lists -- Gleaves/ Rothacker (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Articles, etc. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - LS 385 -- Accreditation (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation of Programs of Education for Librarianship (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Articles, Materials, etc. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Syllabi and Reading Lists (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - ALA -- “Library Education and Personal Utilization” (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - ALA -- COA -- Standards for Accreditation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Selected Readings (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Research (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Library Schools -- Curricula (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - LS 385 -- Experiential Methods in the Teaching of Library Management” (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - LS 385 -- “Notes on Professional Education for Librarianship in the U.S.” (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - ALA -- COA -- Standards for Accreditation, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - International Standards for Library Education.” G. A. Marco (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - LS 385 -- Education for Librarianship -- Articles (Box 11, Folder 37)
- LS 395, LIBRARIAN AND THE PROFESSION FESTSCHRIFT MATERIALS
  - SLA Salary Survey 1976, 77, 78 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Library Journal -- Annual Placement and Salary Report (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - LS 395 (ESG) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - LS 395 -- “Guide to Library Placement Sources” (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - LS 395 -- “Job Prospects in the 1980s” (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - LS 395 -- Placement, etc. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - LS 395 -- Placement, “ALA Guidelines on Professional Placement Practices” (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - LS 395 -- Placement, Sample Letters of Inquiry (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lexington Books -- Contributor’s Resumes, Author Biographies (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - SELA Breakfast at Louisville. Presentation of Festschrift to Frances Neel Cheney (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Festschrift Index (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Article on Festschrift -- Nashville Banner, Nov. 13, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- Biography (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Frances Neel Cheney Award, April 1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- FNC Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- No.3, Post-Publications (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- JMT Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- Royalty Transactions (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- Reviews, Notices, etc. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- No.1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- Lexington Books (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- Announcement, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cheney Festschrift -- No.2, September 1981 -- September 1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lexington Books -- Instructions to Authors (Box 12, Folder 24)
- REVIEWS AND TRANSLATIONS (Drafts and Typescripts)
  - Reviews -- American Reference Book Annual (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Reviews -- American Reference Book Annual (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ARBA Reviews, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Libraries Unlimited ARBA Guide, August 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Reviews for Library Science Annual, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Banner Reviews, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Banner Book Reviews, Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Review of Aunt Julia and the Scriptwriter by Mario Vargas Liosa (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Review of AZTEC, by Gary Jenings (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Review of The Bible and Popular Culture in America, by Allene Stuart Phy (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Review of Brother Enemy, by Speer Morgan (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Review of Chronicle of Death Foretold, by Gabriel Garcia (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Review of Cocktails at Somoza’s and Diplomatic Immunity (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Review of The College Library: A Collection of Essays (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Review of Computer Books and Magazines for the Christmas Season (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The Computer Buyer’s Computer Book Guide (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Review of Congo, by Michael Crichton (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - The Correspondence of Flannery O’Connor and the Brainard Cheneys Nashville Banner (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - The Correspondence for Tennessee Librarian (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Cost -- Effectiveness of Alternative Library Storage Programs (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Review of The Cricket Sings, by Federico G. Lorca (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Review of The Club and Other Stories, by Mario V. Llosa (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Review of Electronic Life: How to Think about Computers, by Michael Crichton (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Review of Emerson’s Library (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Review of Panny, by Erica Jong (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Review of The Fate of the Earth, by Jonathan Schell (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Review of The Fate of the Earth and Nuclear War: What’s in It for You for Christian Home (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Review of A Flag for Sunrise, by Robert Stone (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Review of Folk Songs of the America’s (ESG) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Review of George Eliot; A Reference Guide, by Constance Fulmer (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Review of History of Education, for librarianship in Columbia (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Review of “The Honorary Consul” (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Review of The House of the Spirits, by Isabel Allende (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Review of In Evil Hour, by Gabriel G. Marquez (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Review of Iniciacion En Basic, by William S. Davis (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Review of Lenguaje Basic (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Review of The Library of America (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Review of Louis Shores, Author-Librarian: A Bibliography (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Review of The London Embassy, by Paul Theroux (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Review of Matthew Arnold (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Review of Microforms in Libraries. A Manual for Evaluation and Management, for International Journal of Review in LIS (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Review of Monsignor Quixote, by Graham Greene (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Review of The Mosquito Coast (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Review of Myself As Witness (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Review of North Toward Home (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Review of The Old Gringo, by Carlos Fuentes (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Review of The Peace Book, for Christian Home (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Review of Prisoner Without A Name, Cell Without A Number, by Jacob Timerman (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Review of Research Library Cooperation in the Caribbean (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Review of Russian Journal, by Andrea Lee (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Review of Run with the Horsemen, by Ferrol Sams (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Review of Salvador, by Joan Didion (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Review of Space, by James Michener (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Review of Spanish-Language Books for Public Libraries (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Review of Starting Over (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Review of The Story of the Shipwrecked Sailor, for Nashville Banner (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Review of Target for Research in Library Education (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Review of Theory and Practice in Library Education, by Joe Morehead (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Review of Towers at the Edge of a World, by Virgil Barnett (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Review of Under Cover: An Illustrated History of American Mass Market Paperbacks (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Review of Under the Apple Tree, by Dan Wakefield (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Review of Waging Peace: A Handbook to Abolish Nuclear Weapons, for Christian Home (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Review of Waiting for the Barbarians and Ah. But Your Land Is Beautiful (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Review of Warday, by Whitley Strieber and James Kunetka (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Review of William Morris, A Reference Guide, by Gary L. Aho (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Review of World Librarianship, by Richard Krzys and Gaston Litton (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Review of ALA Encyclopedia (2nd, ed.) -- Translations of Articles on Aguirre, Pessacq, Ruiz, and Sabor (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Translation -- Article on Paraguay (ESG) (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - “Argentina”: Translation of Article for ALA Encyclopedia (2nd, ed.) (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - “Dominican Republic” -- Translation of Article for ALA Encyclopedia (2nd, ed.) (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - “Paraguay” -- Translation of Article for ALA World Encyclopedia, (1984) (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - “Spain” -- Translation for ALA World Encyclopedia for Library and Information Science, (1986) (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Encyclopedia of Library and Information Science (Box 14, Folder 78)
- PUBLICATIONS AND REPORTS, 1967-1984
  - Microcomputers and School Libraries (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mid-State Library Association: A Brief Chronicle (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - “Los Miscrocomputadores y sus Applicaciones Imformaticas” (ESG) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Microformaaulation: A Selected Bibliography of Microforms, 1970-75” (ESG & JRV) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - “A Microforms Program for the Duckworth Libraries of Young Harris College. A Consultant Report” (ESG) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Microform Series Acquisition: A Suggested Plannong Model (ESG & RTC) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - “Micrographics” -- ALA World Encyclopedia of LIS Services (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Micrographics Education: Content, Methodology and Resources for Graduate Course (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Mid-State Library Association: A Brief Chronicle (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Millsaps College (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - More Room at the Top: Librarianship in Light of Asheim’s Proposed Restructure (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - More Room at the Top: Librarianship in Light of Asheim’s Proposed Restructure (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - The Most Useful Reference Source on Latin America: Results of a Survey of Those Who Use Them Most -- The Reference Librarian (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Microforms in Academe” Purdue University, April 5, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)